(Howard:)I don't know.
It's pretty catchy.
(Penny:)Do you even like the Beach Boys?
They have "beach"
right in the name.
(Sheldon:)What do you think?
(Leonard:)Well, now that you can focus
again, what do you say
(Leonard:)we get back to surface tension
of domain walls?
(Sheldon:)Of course. I'm already
seeing a more efficient way
(Sheldon:)of taming the ultravi...
(Sheldon:)I know why
the song was in my head.
(Howard:)Why?
It's about Amy.
(Penny:)Okay, look, I know
Amy's like an old lady,
(Penny:)but she's not old enough
to have a song
from the '60s written about her.
(Sheldon:)It's about
how she made my life better.
(Sheldon:)Consider the lyrics.
"I was living like half a man.
"Then I couldn't love,
but now I can.
"More soul than
"I ever had.
(Sheldon:)I love the way
you soften my life."
Well, she did soften your life,
didn't she?
Yes!
(Sheldon:)She's like
the dryer sheets of my heart!
(Sheldon:)I have to go.
(Raj:)Aw.
(Leonard:)Am I like the dryer
sheets of your heart?